http://www.shopjessicalouise.com/pages/privacy

Privacy Policy
Jessica Louise is committed to safeguarding and respecting your privacy.
This policy (together with our terms of use and any other documents referred to on it) describes the types of personal information we collect on this website, how we may use that information and with whom we may share it. The notice also describes the measures we take to protect the security of the personal information. We also tell you how you can reach us to ask us to (i) access, change or not use the personal information you have provided to us, (ii) withdraw any consent you previously provided to us, (iii) tell us to refrain from communicating with you about our products or services, and (iv) answer any questions you may have about our privacy practices.
Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it. By visiting https://www.shopjessicalouise.com you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy.
1. HOW DO WE COLLECT AND USE YOUR INFORMATION?
1.1 Individuals may choose to provide personal information (such as name, contact details and payment information) through this website and through our customer service line. Here are the ways you may provide the information and the types of information you may submit. We also tell you how we may use the information.
Shopping
1.2 You may be able to purchase Jessica Louise products and gift cards on this website. To process your purchase, we ask for information such as your name, billing and shipping address, telephone number, email address and payment card information. We use this information to process your purchase, confirm your order and deliver the items to you. If you provide us with your prior consent and/or if otherwise permitted under applicable law, we also may use your contact information to communicate with you about our products, services and promotions.
1.3 If you purchase an item on this site or ask us to deliver your purchase to someone else, we ask for the recipient’s name, postal address and email address. We use this information to send the item to the recipient. Before you disclose to us the personal information of another person, you must obtain that person's consent to both the disclosure and the processing of that personal information in accordance with the terms of this policy.
My Account
1.4 You may be able to register to create an account on this website. To do so, we ask for information such as your name and email address. You also may provide your age and gender.
1.5 Through the “my account” feature, you can store billing and shipping information so you won’t have to enter it again when you make another purchase on this site. You also can store payment card information and details of your past purchases.
1.6 You can create and save an address book on your account. You can delete entries in the address book at any time. We will not use or disclose the information you delete from your address book.
Surveys, Competitions and Giveaways
1.7 On this website, you may be able to participate in surveys, competitions, giveaways and other promotions. If you choose to participate in these promotions, we may ask you for information such as your name, email address, postal address and telephone number. We use the information you provide to administer our competitions, giveaways and other promotions. We also may use the information to communicate with you about our products, services and promotions, but only if you have given us your consent to do so.
Electronic Newsletters and Other Marketing Communications
1.8 You may be able to sign up on this site to receive electronic newsletters and promotional emails from Jessica Louise, including new ideas, special offers and event information. To sign up, we may ask you for information such as your name, email address, postal address, telephone number, age, gender, shopping preferences and email preferences. We use this information to send you communications about our products and services, invitations to specials sales and events at stores located near you, and notices of new arrivals. We also use this information to tailor our newsletters to reflect your preferences.
1.9 You can choose at any time not to receive marketing emails from us by clicking on the unsubscribe link within our marketing emails. You also may use the email preferences section of the “my account” feature to opt out of receiving marketing emails or to specify which, if any, communications you would like to receive from us. There is no charge to you to unsubscribe.
Blogs
1.10 You may be able to submit comments to blogs we host on this website. You may include personal information in your comment, and you also may submit your name with your comment. We use your name to identify you as a commenter.
Email to a Friend
1.11 You may be able to share certain content from this website with your friends. To send information to your friends, we may ask for your friends’ and your email addresses. We use this information only to fulfil your request. We do not retain the information you provide in connection with this feature, except to send the requested content. We will not include any other advertisements within the messages sent to your friends.
Contact Us
1.12 If you communicate with us through the “Contact Us” link on this site, we may ask you for information such as your name, email address, and telephone number. We use this information to respond to and communicate with you about your questions and comments.
Cookies, Web Beacons and other Information We Collect by Automated Means
1.13 We obtain certain information by automated means when you visit our website, such as the IP address of the device you use to connect to the Internet and the pages accessed. By collecting this information, we learn how to best tailor our website to our visitors and understand what products and services you might prefer. We collect this information through various means, such as “cookies” and “web beacons.”
Cookies Like many companies, we use “cookies” on this website. Cookies are bits of text that are placed on your computer’s hard drive when you visit certain websites. Cookies may enhance your online experience by saving your preferences while you are visiting a particular site. We use cookies, for example, to preserve the contents of your virtual shopping bag between visits. We also use cookies to measure activity on the site and determine which areas and features of the site are the most popular.
Web Beacons Certain pages on this website contain "web beacons" (also known as Internet tags, pixel tags and clear GIFs). Web beacons are often used in combination with cookies. We use them for internal purposes, such as to obtain the IP address of the computer that downloaded the page on which the beacon appears, the URL of the page on which the beacon appears, the time the page containing the beacon was viewed, and the type of browser used to view the page. We also retain service providers who use web beacons to assess the effectiveness of our email communications and learn what pages our visitors viewed. Unlike cookies, you cannot decline web beacons. However, setting your browser to decline cookies or to prompt you for a response will keep web beacons from tracking your activity.
Performance Tools We may use performance tools such as Google Analytics to measure the effectiveness of our advertising and determine how visitors use this website. Google Analytics tools, including cookies and web beacons, allow us to collect information such as the state/country of residence and zip code/postcode from which our visitors come and the IP addresses of our visitors' computers. You can opt out of aggregation and analysis of data collected by companies like Google Analytics.
1.14 To find out more about the way we use cookies, web beacons and similar technologies, and how to manage your settings and preferences, please visit our Cookie Policy.
Customer Assistance
1.15 You may call our customer service line for information about our products or personal shopping advice. If you do so, we may ask you for information such as your name, email address, postal address, telephone number and, if you choose to make a purchase, your payment card information. We use this information to respond to your request and process your transaction.
Third Party Sources
1.16 In addition to the ways we collect information about you described above, we also may obtain information about you from third parties (for example, our sub-contractors in technical, payment and delivery services via PayPal. We will share information with such service providers only to the extent necessary for them to provide their relevant service (in this instance, processing payments made via our website, refunding such payments and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments and refunds).
1.17 We may also use your personal information to provide you with products or services you request (such as tailoring services or processing returns), enhance your shopping experience and communicate with you about our products, services and promotions.
1.18 In addition, we may use your personal information for internal purposes, such as fraud and theft prevention, accident reporting, development and administration of our sites and stores, data analytics, and compliance with our legal obligations, policies and procedures.
2. HOW DO WE SHARE YOUR INFORMATION?
2.1 We do not sell or otherwise disclose personal information about our customers, except as described here.
2.2 We may share the personal information with any member of our group, which means our subsidiaries, our ultimate holding company and all its subsidiaries.
2.3 We will not share your information with  third parties
2.4 We may also disclose information about you, if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our terms of use, our terms and conditions of supply, and/or any of our other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Jessica Louise, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
3. HOW DO WE PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?
3.1 All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Any payment transactions will be encrypted.
3.2 Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.
3.3 Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.
3.4 Children under the age of eighteen may not shop on this website without the consent of their legal representatives.
4. HOW CAN YOU ACCESS, AMEND OR CORRECT THE INFORMATION WE HOLD ON YOU?
4.1 Please let us know if the personal information that we hold about you needs to be corrected or updated. You may contact us as specified in the “How Do You Contact Us” section below, and instruct us to provide you with any personal information we hold about you. Please include in your request, your name, email address, postal address, a copy of a utility bill showing your current address or other proof of address, and a copy of your identity card or passport certified by a solicitor or bank. Any access request may be subject to a fee of USD $5 to meet our costs in providing you with details of the information we hold about you.
4.2 Subject to applicable law, we may limit or deny you access to personal information where providing such access is unreasonably burdensome or expensive under the circumstances.
4.3 You may also choose not to receive marketing communications from us by clicking on the unsubscribe link in our marketing emails or contacting us as specified in the “How Do You Contact Us” section below. Please include your name, email address and postal address if you send us your request by email or postal mail.
5. DO WE LINK TO OTHER SITES?
5.1 This website may, from time to time, contain links to and from third party websites, for your convenience and information. These sites may be operated by companies not affiliated with Jessica Louise. Linked sites may have their own privacy policies, which we strongly suggest you review if you visit any of these linked websites. We have no control over, and are not responsible for the content of any websites that are not affiliated with Fred Perry, any use of those websites, or the privacy practices of such third party websites.
7. HOW DO WE UPDATE OUR PRIVACY POLICY?
7.1 This Privacy Policy may be updated periodically and without prior notice to you to reflect changes in our personal information practices or relevant laws. Where appropriate, we will post a prominent notice on the site to notify you of any significant changes to our policy and indicate at the top of the notice when it was updated.
7.2 Please check back frequently to see any updates or changes to our privacy policy.
8. HOW DO YOU CONTACT US?
8.1 If you have any questions or comments about this policy, or if you would like us to update information we have about you or your preferences, please contact us as indicated below:
Contact form: here
Telephone: 213-489-1066
Email: info@jessicalouise.com
Address: 117 W 9th St #201 LA CA 90015
Home
Gift Card
Catalog
Accessories
